<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Study on Gary&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Study on Gary&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.141.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 09:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CS/AI PhD Jobs Update 2025-11-26</title>
      <link>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/phd_2025-11-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/phd_2025-11-26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;assistant-professor-in-integrated-semiconductor-device-and-chip-technologies-kth&#34;&gt;Assistant professor in Integrated semiconductor device and chip technologies (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/847755?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/847755?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Teach at both undergraduate and graduate levels; Carry out independent research; Contribute actively to the operations and development of the cleanroom infrastructure at KTH&amp;rsquo;s Electrum Laboratory; Method development, deployment, and optimization of process flows and strategies for semiconductor devices and integrated circuits; Cooperate with academic and industrial actors and laboratory operational staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Completed a doctorate or equivalent scientific competence; Prioritized candidates who completed qualifications a maximum of seven years before the deadline; Consideration for other candidates may be based on special reasons such as illness, parental leave, or similar circumstances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Scientific publications; Curriculum vitae; Cover letter; Names and contact information of references&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS/AI PhD Jobs Update 2025-11-25</title>
      <link>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/phd_2025-11-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 09:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/phd_2025-11-25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-students-in-integrated-tn-ntn-6g-and-beyond-networks-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral students in integrated TN-NTN 6G and beyond networks (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/861362?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/861362?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Focus on distributed MIMO in space, exploring novel concepts for antenna cooperation and beamforming in satellite constellations.Address terrestrial–non-terrestrial (TN–NTN) integration and network design.Investigate the joint management of cloud, processing, and radio resources in space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (for example a master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits.At least 60 second-cycle higher education credits or substantially equivalent knowledge.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.Goal oriented and persevering in your work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Complete application in accordance with KTH&amp;rsquo;s recruitment system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-students-in-theoretical-foundations-of-data-storage-and-analysis-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral students in theoretical foundations of data storage and analysis (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869297?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869297?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct research in algorithms, data structures, and data analysisanalyze algorithms theoreticallycollaborate with supervisors and other researcherspresent research results at international conferences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Master of Science degree or equivalentstrong background and interest in algorithm design and mathematicsgood command of Englishpersonal skills such as goal orientation, perseverance, and collaboration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experienceapplication letter (maximum 2 pages); copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received by the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-sic-bipolar-devices-for-power-electronics-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in SiC bipolar devices for power electronics (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868812?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868812?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The position involves fabrication and characterization of new devices in KTH’s Electrum Laboratory with a focus on semiconductor process technology to enhance device performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be admitted to postgraduate education, the applicant must have passed a second cycle degree (for example a master&amp;rsquo;s degree), or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, of which at least 60 second-cycle higher education credits, or acquired substantially equivalent knowledge. A mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6 is also required. Experience of power semiconductor devices and semiconductor process technology is meritorious.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge.Application letter with a brief description of research interests (maximum 2 pages long).Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies and certificates of fulfilled language requirements.Translations into English or Swedish if the original document is in another language. Copies of originals must be certified.Representative publications or technical reports with a summary and a web link for longer documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-machine-learning-for-robotic-manipulation-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Machine Learning for Robotic Manipulation (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869586?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869586?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Develop novel approaches for robotic manipulation experiments.Establish large-scale real-world robotic manipulation datasets.Benchmark research results to establish reliable ground truth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree or completed 240 higher education credits.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.Goal oriented and persevering.Ability to independently pursue work, collaborate with others, analyze and work with complex issues.Strong emphasis on personal skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge.Application letter (maximum 2 pages) describing research interests, past studies, and future goals.Representative publications or technical reports, with a summary and a web link for longer documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-electrochemical-sensing-and-control-for-organs-on-chips-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Electrochemical Sensing and Control for Organs-on-Chips (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/867956?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/867956?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The doctoral research project will focus on the design and development of electrochemical sensors and electrochemical actuators, along with the requisite testing and characterization. You will collaborate closely with other members of the multidisciplinary team on the relevant Organ-on-Chip integration and biological application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be admitted to postgraduate education, the applicant must have basic eligibility in accordance with either a second cycle degree or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, of which at least 60 are second-cycle higher education credits, or equivalent knowledge. Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies and certificates of fulfilled language requirements. Translations into English or Swedish if the original document is not issued in one of these languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-polymer-technology-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Polymer Technology (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868704?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868704?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The doctoral student will gain experience both in fundamental research and practical application development, synthesize, integrate, and apply high-performance barrier layers to be used on moulded cellulose fibre products, as well as understand and model structure and properties during synthesis, lamination, use, and recycling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (for example a master&amp;rsquo;s degree), or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, of which at least 60 second-cycle higher education credits, or acquired substantially equivalent knowledge.Completed university-level course in polymer chemistry, materials chemistry, or polymer technology.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.Candidates must not have resided or conducted their main activity (work, studies, etc.) in Sweden for more than 12 months in the 3 years immediately preceding the recruitment date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Documents to submit were not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Application deadline was not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement, with additional mobility and possible family allowances.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-solid-mechanics-modelling-of-cellulose-fibre-networks-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Solid Mechanics: Modelling of cellulose fibre networks (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869544?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869544?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Develop a physics-based numerical model for deformation and damage analysis in cellulose fiber networksenable advanced materials design and manufacturing toolsaddress fundamental fiber network mechanics challenges and provide validated models for industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Candidates must have a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or 240 higher education credits including at least 60 second-cycle creditsmust not have resided or conducted work/studies in Sweden for more than 12 months in the last 3 yearsmust have English proficiency equivalent to English B/6desirable qualifications include proficiency in numerical methods (FEM) and programming (Python, Matlab, C++, Fortran); background in mechanics of materials or computational modellinginterest in interdisciplinary collaboration and potential for teaching/laboratory work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV, cover letter, relevant degree certificates, and other supporting documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreementincludes a mobility allowance and possible family allowance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-solid-mechanics-with-a-focus-on-data-driven-methods-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Solid Mechanics with a focus on data-driven methods (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869595?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869595?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Develop an AI-based hybrid tool for diagnosis and prognosis in dry forming of cellulose fibresCombine experimental data with physics-based modelsBridge the gap between advanced simulations and industrial product developmentGain experience in both basic research and industrial applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Basic eligibility as per Swedish Higher Education OrdinanceMobility rules: Candidates must not have resided or conducted their main activity in Sweden for more than 12 months in the last 3 yearsCompleted a second cycle degree or equivalent qualificationEnglish proficiency equivalent to English B/6Personal capabilities: goal-oriented, persevering, able to independently pursue work, collaboration skills, professional approach, analytical and problem-solving skillsAdvantageous qualifications: Proficiency in numerical methods (FEM), programming (Python, Matlab, C++, Fortran), background in mechanics of materials or computational modeling, experience with machine learning for physical fields/PDEs/GNNs and HPC workflows, interest in interdisciplinary collaboration, potential for teaching/laboratory work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterCopies of degree certificatesTranscripts of recordsProof of English proficiency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement, includes additional allowances such as a mobility allowance and possible family allowance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;double-degree-phd-student-in-chemistry-with-specialization-in-polymer-electrolytes-for-batteries-kth&#34;&gt;Double degree PhD student in Chemistry with specialization in polymer electrolytes for batteries (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869881?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869881?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Experimental studies of polymer electrolytes, primarily solid-state, for applications in Li-based batteries.Polymer synthesis, electrolyte fabrication, construction and testing of prototype battery cells.Materials characterization techniques (spectroscopy, structural characterization).Electrochemical characterization of both electrolytes and cells.Coursework and possible teaching or other departmental duties (maximum 20%).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, including at least 60 second-cycle credits.Passed courses of chemistry or relevant areas totaling a minimum of 90 higher education credits (60 at advanced level and 30 within chemistry).Degree project of at least 15 credits.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.Previous experience with polymers and polymer materials, experience with batteries (especially Li-batteries), and general experience in materials chemistry and electrochemistry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Application to Uppsala University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the job text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the job text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-advanced-characterisationmodelling-of-tungsten-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Advanced characterisation/modelling of tungsten (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/859676?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/859676?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Develop thermodynamic and kinetic descriptions of tungsten and its alloysIntegrate results into microstructure models to predict phase transformations and grain structure during electron beam powder bed fusionValidate models in close collaboration with experimental researchersCharacterise tungsten and its alloys at the atomic level using techniques such as atom probe tomography (APT) and electron-ion microscopyIdentify and understand the effects of trace and alloying elements on microstructure and propertiesLink experimental data to microstructure modelling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Master’s degree in Materials Science or a related fieldBasic eligibility as per the Swedish Higher Education OrdinanceMandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6Ability to independently pursue work, collaborate with others, and analyze complex issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterTranscripts and diplomasReferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement, with possible mobility and family allowances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-students-in-theoretical-condensed-matter-physics-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral students in Theoretical Condensed Matter Physics (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/852011?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/852011?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct research using analytical and numerical methods in theoretical condensed matter physics.Collaborate with local and international theoretical and experimental groups.Pursue independent work and analyze complex issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (e.g., a master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, including at least 60 second-cycle higher education credits.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.Ability to work collaboratively and professionally, and possess personal skills relevant to doctoral studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge.Application letter (maximum 2 pages) describing motivation for research studies, academic interests, and goals.Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies and certificates of fulfilled language requirements.Translations into English or Swedish if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received by the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-socio-technical-studies-of-conversational-robots-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Socio-technical studies of conversational robots (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/871088?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/871088?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct user studies on the integration of AI-driven conversational robots within elderly care, explore the benefits and tensions across technical, ethical, and regulatory aspects, assess the impact of robots on care workflows, and develop a proposal for a Nordic Model for sustainable robot integration in long-term care. Publish results in high-quality peer-reviewed journals and present at scientific conferences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be admitted to postgraduate education, the applicant must have basic eligibility in accordance with either passed a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, with at least 60 second-cycle higher education credits. Preferred qualifications include experience in conducting user studies with robots or AI-driven technologies, experience in social science methodologies, good communication skills, and a mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies and certificates of fulfilled language requirements. Translations into English or Swedish if the original document is not issued in one of these languages. CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge. Application letter with a brief description of research interests and future goals (maximum 2 pages). Representative publications or technical reports with summaries for longer documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-astrophysics-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Astrophysics (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/866832?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/866832?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The PhD student will work in the field supernova remnants, addressing questions related to explosion physics, compact objects and circumstellar interaction. The work will primarily involve analysis and modelling of observational data. Observations from a range of different telescopes will be used, including the James Webb Space Telescope.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be admitted to postgraduate education, the applicant must have basic eligibility in accordance with either: passed a second cycle degree (e.g., a master&amp;rsquo;s degree), or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, of which at least 60 second-cycle higher education credits, or acquired substantially equivalent knowledge. The basic eligibility should be in either astronomy or physics. In addition, a mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6 is needed. A MSc project in astronomy, experience of analysis of astronomical data, and excellent written and oral communication skills are particularly important. Personal skills will also be greatly emphasized.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledgeapplication letter (maximum 2 pages); copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studiescertificates of fulfilled language requirementstranslations into English or Swedish if the original document is not issued in one of these languagescopies of originals must be certifiedrepresentative publications or technical reports, with summaries and web links for longer documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received by the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-the-design-of-interaction-synchrony-with-soft-robotics-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in the Design of Interaction Synchrony with Soft Robotics (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868290?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868290?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Design and demonstrate prototypes for interaction and touch with soft robotics and haptic technologiesWork towards interactional synchrony between the body and moving materialsAnalyze and work with complex design issuesCollaborate with others in an interdisciplinary team of designers and engineersDraw from critical, feminist theories to stimulate the design processUtilize creative and playful methods in the design processDesign and develop medium-fidelity physical prototypes for design workshops&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Human Computer Interaction or related subject) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, including at least 60 second-cycle higher education creditsEquivalent knowledge acquired in another wayMandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6Goal-oriented and persevering in work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledgeApplication letter (maximum 2 pages) describing interest in research studies, academic interests, and relation to previous studies and future goalsCopies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies and certificates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received by the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-architectural-technology-and-design-technologies-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Architectural Technology and Design Technologies (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868833?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868833?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct research in advanced design technologies and design-based research.Participate in various research projects and develop an individual topic.Engage in teaching opportunities within the architectural program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Basic eligibility in accordance with Swedish Higher Education Ordinance: a second cycle degree or equivalent knowledge.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.Experience as a practicing architect or in computational design development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge.Application letter (maximum 2 pages) describing research interests and future goals.Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received by the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-probabilistic-machine-learning-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Probabilistic Machine Learning (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869866?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869866?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Work on the reliability and trustworthiness of machine learning modelsDevelop theoretical and methodological work to improve the reliability and trustworthiness of those modelsDevelop open-source librariesPublish in top-tier machine learning venuesCollaborate with researchers working on trustworthy machine learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (e.g., a master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, including at least 60 second-cycle higher education creditsStrong mathematical and programming skillsStrong background in machine learning, statistics, linear algebra, and optimizationFirst research experience through peer-reviewed publicationsEnglish equivalent to English B/6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Copies of diplomasCurriculum VitaePersonal letterResearch proposal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-large-language-model-inferencing-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Large Language Model inferencing (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869680?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869680?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Design, implementation, and evaluation of distributed systems and networks for machine learning inference.Applying machine learning concepts to devise agentic frameworks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits (at least 60 second-cycle credits).English proficiency equivalent to English B/6.Knowledge of systems and networking is highly desirable.Personal skills such as being goal-oriented, persevering, and capable of independent work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge.Application letter (maximum 2 pages) describing research interests and goals.Copies of diplomas and grades from previous studies and certificates of language requirements (translated if necessary).Representative publications or technical reports with summaries and links to full texts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-electrical-engineering-to-the-department-of-electrical-and-information-technology-pa20252605-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Electrical Engineering to the Department of Electrical and Information Technology  (PA2025/2605) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:856834/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:856834/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Perform research and teaching within the Cybersecurity and Privacy areaDevote yourself to your doctoral programme, including participation in research projects and third cycle courses, seminars, and conferencesConduct cybersecurity researchContribute to research projectsTake doctoral students coursesParticipate in teaching and other departmental work (maximum of 20% of working hours)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Awarded a second-cycle qualificationSatisfy the requirements for courses comprising at least 240 credits, with at least 60 credits awarded in the second cycleAcquire substantially equivalent knowledge in some other way&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterTranscripts of recordsOther relevant documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-electrical-engineering-focusing-on-design-of-radio-frequency-integrated-circuits-to-the-department-of-electrical-and-information-technology-pa20253080-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Electrical Engineering focusing on design of radio frequency integrated circuits to the Department of Electrical and Information Technology (PA2025/3080) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:870960/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:870960/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; You will primarily devote yourself to your doctoral programme, which includes participation in research projects as well as third cycle courses, seminars and conferences. Your research will focus on design of radio frequency integrated circuits. You will develop new solutions on circuit and architecture level, design and simulate circuits, design chip layout and passive components with EM-simulations, and set up and perform measurements in the lab. You will cooperate with other ELLIIT researchers, especially with the corresponding doctoral student in Linköping in analog and radio frequency integrated circuit design, and also with researchers in digital circuits and wireless systems. You will write scientific papers and present them at international conferences and publish in international journals. Furthermore, you will take doctoral student courses to deepen your knowledge in integrated circuit design, CAD tools, wireless systems, and other relevant areas. The duties also include participation in teaching and other departmental work (however, a maximum of 20% of working hours).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be eligible for admission and employment as a doctoral student, you must fulfil the requirements below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Please submit your application including a CV, motivation letter, copies of relevant degrees, and contact information for at least two references.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; The application deadline is not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; The salary for this position is not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-physics-within-thz-electron-spin-resonance-ellipsometry-pa20253292-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Physics within THz-electron spin resonance-ellipsometry (PA2025/3292) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:875564/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:875564/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; You will primarily devote yourself to your doctoral programme, which includes participation in research projects as well as third cycle courses, seminars and conferences. The aim of the PhD project is to conduct research in THz material analysis to expand the scope of THz ellipsometry and optical Hall effect to electron spin resonance ellipsometry. The method will mainly be applied in materials science, in particular for the investigation of crystal phases and defects in semiconductors. In addition to nitride material systems, a focus area will be Ga2O3 and other ultrawide bandgap semiconductors. The duties also include participation in teaching and other departmental work (however, a maximum of 20% of working hours).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; A person meets the general admission requirements for third-cycle courses and study programmes if the applicant has been awarded a second-cycle qualification, or has satisfied the requirements for courses comprising at least 240 credits of which at least 60 credits were awarded in the second cycle, or has acquired substantially equivalent knowledge in some other way in Sweden or abroad.A person meets the specific admission requirements for third cycle studies in physics if the applicant has at least 30 second-cycle credits of relevance to the subject, of which at least 15 credits shall come from advanced courses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterTranscriptsReferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-human-rights-studies-pa20253092-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Human Rights Studies (PA2025/3092) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871292/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871292/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studiesDepartmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks (maximum 20%).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements are specified in the general syllabusability to benefit from doctoral studies assessed against the criteria of quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-old-testament-studies-or-in-philosophy-of-religion-and-ethics-pa20253108-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Old Testament Studies or in Philosophy of Religion and Ethics (PA2025/3108) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871350/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871350/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Participate in the relevant subject&amp;rsquo;s research seminarBe regularly present at the departmentFulfill departmental work such as teaching and administrative tasks (maximum 20% of the position)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Old Testament Studies and Philosophy of Religion and Ethics as specified in the general syllabusAbility to benefit from doctoral studies assessed against criteria of quality, quantity, progression, and relevance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationsCover letterRecords of previous studiesDocumentation of language skillsAcademic papers / degree projectsAny scholarly publicationsProject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-archaeology-pa20253088-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Archaeology (PA2025/3088) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871269/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871269/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Archeology are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-jewish-studies-with-a-specialisation-in-late-antiquity-pa20253089-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Jewish Studies with a Specialisation in Late Antiquity (PA2025/3089) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871280/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871280/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Take an active part in the department’s seminars and research activities related to Late Antiquity.Engage in departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks (maximum of 20% work assignment).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Primary expertise in Judaism of Late Antiquity.Experience with Late Antique Christian sources or Jewish–Christian interactions during the period approximately 200–700 CE is preferred.Ability to integrate both textual and archaeological evidence in research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationsCover letterRecords of previous studiesDocumentation of language skillsAcademic papers / degree projectsAny scholarly publicationsProject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-practical-philosophy-pa20253090-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Practical Philosophy (PA2025/3090) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871286/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871286/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies and departmental work such as teaching and administrative tasks (maximum 20%).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Practical Philosophy are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily consider applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-cognitive-science-pa20253091-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Cognitive Science (PA2025/3091) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871290/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871290/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studiesdepartmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned (maximum 20% work).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Cognitive Science are specified in the general syllabusapplicants&amp;rsquo; ability to benefit from doctoral studies will be assessed against quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-ethnology-pa20253093-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Ethnology (PA2025/3093) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871299/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871299/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Ethnology are specified in the general syllabus, available at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ht.lu.se/en/utbildning/forskarutbildning/dina-doktorandstudier/general-syllabi/&#34;&gt;https://www.ht.lu.se/en/utbildning/forskarutbildning/dina-doktorandstudier/general-syllabi/&lt;/a&gt;. Assessment criteria include quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualifications, cover letter, records of previous studies, documentation of language skills, academic papers / degree projects, any scholarly publications, project plan. Please note that you need to upload all documents with your application in PDF format.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-art-history-and-visual-studies-pa20253094-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Art History and Visual Studies (PA2025/3094) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871306/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871306/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Art History and Visual Studies are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV/list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers/degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-slavic-languages-with-a-specialisation-in-polish-literature-or-ukrainian-literature-pa20253102-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Slavic Languages with a specialisation in Polish Literature or Ukrainian Literature (PA2025/3102) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871331/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871331/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies and departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Knowledge of contemporary Ukrainian literature or Polish literature is considered a merit. Comparative research projects involving both Polish and Ukrainian literatures, including reception and/or translation studies, will be given priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-media-history-within-the-national-graduate-school-of-historical-studies-pa20253105-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Media History, within The National Graduate School of Historical Studies (PA2025/3105) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871344/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871344/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The doctoral student will be part of the national Graduate School of Historical Studies. Work assignments include doctoral studies and departmental work such as teaching and administrative tasks, with a maximum of 20% allocated to such work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Media History are specified in the general syllabus. Applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies will be assessed based on quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-history-within-the-national-graduate-school-of-historical-studies-pa20253103-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in History, within The National Graduate School of Historical Studies (PA2025/3103) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871337/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871337/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned, with a maximum amount of such work being 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in History are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-practical-theology-specialising-in-recruiting-for-professional-ministry-pa20253106-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Practical Theology, specialising in recruiting for professional ministry (PA2025/3106) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871347/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871347/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Participate in the research seminar in Church History and Practical Theology at CTRBe regularly present at the departmentCarry out departmental work such as teaching and administrative tasks, up to 20% of the time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Fluency in Swedish or another Scandinavian languageAbility to benefit from third cycle studies as assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression, and relevance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationsCover letterRecords of previous studiesDocumentation of language skillsAcademic papers / degree projectsAny scholarly publicationsProject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-english-literature-pa20253101-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in English Literature (PA2025/3101) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871330/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871330/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in English Literature are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against quality, quantity, progression and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-general-linguistics-pa20253099-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in General Linguistics (PA2025/3099) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871325/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871325/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies and departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in General Linguistics are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily consider the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-literature-pa20253098-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Literature (PA2025/3098) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871320/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871320/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Literature are specified in the general syllabus. Good proficiency in Swedish is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-one-of-the-following-specialisations-french-studies-with-a-specialisation-in-didactics-french-studies-with-a-specialisation-in-linguistics-or-modern-greek-studies-with-a-specialisation-in-linguistics-pa20253097-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in one of the following specialisations: French Studies with a specialisation in Didactics, French Studies with a specialisation in Linguistics, or Modern Greek Studies with a specialisation in Linguistics (PA2025/3097) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871315/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871315/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies and departmental work, including teaching and administrative tasks (maximum 20%).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in French Studies and Modern Greek Studies are specified in the respective general syllabus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic paper / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-history-of-ideas-and-sciences-pa20253096-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in History of Ideas and Sciences (PA2025/3096) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871312/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871312/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studiesDepartmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in History of Ideas and Sciences are specified in the general syllabusapplicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies assessed against quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-student-in-working-environment-with-a-focus-on-digitalisation-pa20252877-lund&#34;&gt;PhD student in working environment, with a focus on digitalisation (PA2025/2877) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:865044/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:865044/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Devote yourself to the doctoral programmeParticipation in research projects as well as third cycle courses, seminars, and conferencesConduct literature reviews on mental ill-health among children and young peopleConduct semi-structured interviews and focus-group discussions with psychologists and school counsellorsAnalyze how digitalisation affects workload, professional responsibility, and the experience of providing ‘good care’Produce guidance material that documents the project and research resultsIteratively test the results with target groups in the sector through feedback meetingsContribute to teaching and other departmental work (up to 20% of working time)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Fulfill general admission requirements for third-cycle courses and study programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterAcademic transcriptsResearch proposalReferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-theoretical-computer-science-andor-combinatorial-optimization-pa20253338-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in theoretical computer science and/or combinatorial optimization (PA2025/3338) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:876903/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:876903/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; You will primarily devote yourself to your doctoral programme, which includes participation in research projects as well as third cycle courses, seminars and conferences. The main tasks and responsibilities consist of conducting mathematical research and/or algorithm design and development. The work duties also include teaching and other departmental duties (no more than 20%), in which case the position is prolonged accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be eligible for admission and employment as a doctoral student, you must fulfil the requirements below. A person meets the general admission requirements for third-cycle courses and study programmes if the applicant has been awarded a second-cycle qualification, or has satisfied the requirements for courses comprising at least 240 credits of which at least 60 credits were awarded in the second cycle, or has acquired substantially equivalent knowledge in some other way in Sweden or abroad. Applicants meet the specific admission requirements for third cycle studies in computer science if they have at least 60 second-cycle credits at an advanced level with relevance for the research topic, or an MSc in Engineering in Computer Science and Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Information and Communication Technology, Engineering Physics or Engineering.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;at-least-one-phd-position-at-the-sociology-of-law-department-pa20253009-lund&#34;&gt;At least one PHD position at the Sociology of Law Department (PA2025/3009) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:868967/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:868967/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Focus on PhD studies and work on the dissertation in Sociology of Law.Participate actively in the department’s research environment.Perform teaching and administrative duties, up to a maximum of 20% of full-time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Master’s degree in Sociology of Law or another relevant subject.Minimum of 240 ECTS credits, with at least 60 at the advanced level.At least 30 ECTS credits in Sociology of Law at an advanced level.Excellent ability to express oneself in spoken and written English.Strong motivation and ability to work independently under pressure.Good collaboration and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Cover letter in Swedish or English (max 1,000 words).Thesis equivalent to at least 15 ECTS credits at the advanced level in Sociology of Law or a subject deemed equivalent.Summary of the thesis if written in a language other than Swedish, Danish, Norwegian, or English (max 1,000 words).CV in Swedish or English showing eligibility for PhD studies.Degree certificates and transcripts in Swedish or English.Brief research plan of max 13,000 characters including spaces and references.Names and contact details of two referees.Any other documents to support the application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Fixed-term employment for four years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-in-sociology-of-law--authoritarian-governance-in-central-asia-pa20253055-lund&#34;&gt;PhD in Sociology of Law – Authoritarian Governance in Central Asia (PA2025/3055) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:870095/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:870095/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct independent research within the scope of the project.Undertake fieldwork in Central Asia and two mandatory secondments (one academic, one non-academic) abroad.Participate in training events, workshops, and conferences organized by the SOCIAL Doctoral Network.Collaborate with international supervisors and peers.Contribute to departmental activities, including teaching and seminars (up to 20% of working hours).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; A completed degree at the advanced level in Sociology of Law or another subject deemed relevant by the employer.Doctoral candidates cannot have been awarded a doctoral degree and/or completed more than four years of full-time equivalent research experience.Must not have resided or carried out their main activity (i.e. work, studies) in the hosting country for more than 12 months in the 3 years immediately before the recruitment date.A minimum of 240 credits, of which at least 60 must be at the advanced level.At least 30 credits in Sociology of Law or a related subject at the advanced level, including a thesis of at least 15 credits.Excellent ability to express yourself in spoken and written English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterTranscriptsTwo letters of recommendation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-in-sociology-of-authoritarian-law--outside-the-law-legal-mobilization-in-central-asia-pa20253042-lund&#34;&gt;PhD in Sociology of Authoritarian Law – “Outside the Law” Legal Mobilization in Central Asia (PA2025/3042) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:869875/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:869875/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct independent research within the scope of the project.Undertake fieldwork in Central Asia and two mandatory secondments (one academic, one non-academic) abroad.Participate in training events, workshops, and conferences organized by the SOCIAL Doctoral Network.Collaborate with international supervisors and peers.Contribute to departmental activities, including teaching and seminars (up to 20% of working hours).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; generalspecific&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterOfficial transcriptsProposal for research project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-position-in-experimental-physics-umea&#34;&gt;PhD position in  Experimental Physics (Umea)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/phd-position-in-experimental-physics_869672/&#34;&gt;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/phd-position-in-experimental-physics_869672/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The main assignment for the doctoral student is to be part of the research education, including participation in the described research project and taking relevant courses. Teaching and other departmental work (up to a maximum of 20%) can be included.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be admitted for studies at third-cycle level, a second-cycle level degree or completed course requirements of at least 240 ECTS credits (60 at second-cycle level) is required. A minimum of 120 ECTS need to be within the physics subject area. Applicants with master degrees in other subjects such as Chemistry, Material Science or Physical Engineering are also welcomed if the above requirements are fulfilled. Competence and experience in experimental research, material synthesis, characterization, and spectroscopy are advantageous. Previous work with lanthanides/actinides, carbon materials, and good communication skills in English are mandatory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; A cover letter with a summary of research interests and motivation (max. 1 page)Curriculum VitaeCertified copies of relevant degree certificates translated to English or SwedishTranscripts with grades, in English or Swedish translation, with a brief explanation of the grading system for international applicants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2025-12-01&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; The salary is fixed according to the established salary level for doctoral students.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-position-in-chemistry-with-a-specialization-in-environmental-chemistry-umea&#34;&gt;PhD position in Chemistry, with a specialization in Environmental Chemistry (Umea)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/phd-position-in-chemistry-with-a-specialization-in-environmental-chemistry_871188/&#34;&gt;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/phd-position-in-chemistry-with-a-specialization-in-environmental-chemistry_871188/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The thesis project will focus on the fate of PFAS in thermochemical conversion and associated processes of biomass and industrial waste materials. The overarching aim of the project is to elucidate the fate, distribution, and degradation pathways of PFAS during thermochemical conversion of PFAS-containing biomass and waste feedstocks, and to assess their potential presence in process outputs. The research will include combustion experiments in lab set-ups, utilizing real and model waste feedstocks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be admitted for studies at third-cycle level you are required to have completed a second-cycle level degree or equivalent education from abroad. You must have completed first-cycle courses of at least 90 ECTS credits within the field of chemistry or another directly relevant subject. Very good command of the English language, both written and spoken. Additional qualifications include training and/or experience in environmental chemistry, analytical chemistry, combustion chemistry, or organic chemistry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; The specific documents to submit are not detailed in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-02&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; The salary or contract details are not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-2-phd-students-for-the-department-of-political-science-umea&#34;&gt;1-2 PhD students for the Department of Political Science (Umea)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/1-2-phd-students-for-the-department-of-political-science_860718/&#34;&gt;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/1-2-phd-students-for-the-department-of-political-science_860718/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct research in political science or peace and conflict studiesParticipate in departmental activitiesDevelop a research plan as part of the applicationPotentially engage in teaching up to 20% of the time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Earned a degree at the advanced levelCompleted course requirements for at least 240 ECTS pointsAt least 60 ECTS points at the advanced levelAt least 90 ECTS points in peace and conflict studies or political scienceProficient in oral and written communication in EnglishStrong analytical, communicative, critical, and independent skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Cover letter summarizing qualifications, research interests, and reasons for applying (max two pages)Research proposal of 3-5 pages discussing potential research problem, purpose, theory, and empirical dataCV / curriculum vitaeCertified transcripts of academic records and degrees1-3 writing samples in Swedish or English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Temporary position, extent 100%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-research-fellow-in-pharmaceutical-analytical-chemistry-oslo&#34;&gt;PhD Research Fellow in (Pharmaceutical) analytical chemistry (Oslo)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/289658/phd-research-fellow-in-pharmaceutical-analytical-chemistry&#34;&gt;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/289658/phd-research-fellow-in-pharmaceutical-analytical-chemistry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The candidate will work with implementing Molecularly Imprinted Polymers (MIPs) in the sample preparation workflow of bottom-up liquid chromatography-mass spectrometry (LC-MS) analysis of established disease biomarkers. Novel MIP-assays developed in the project will be validated against conventional assays. The project will mainly be conducted at the Department of Pharmacy, University of Oslo, but will include secondments to Proteome Sciences, Frankfurt, University of Strathclyde, Glasgow, and Capitainer AB, Sweden.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Master&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent in (bio)analytical chemistry at the moment of appointmentForeign completed degree (M.Sc.-level) corresponding to a minimum of four years in the Norwegian educational system in (bio)analytical chemistryExperience with LC-MS and sample preparation preferable from biological samplesFluent oral and written communication skills in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Cover letterCurriculum vitaeMaster&amp;rsquo;s degree certificateTranscripts from previous educationList of references&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; November 30, 2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Salary according to the University of Oslo guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-research-fellow-in-computational-neurosciencebrain-physics-oslo&#34;&gt;PhD Research Fellow in computational neuroscience/brain physics (Oslo)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/290338/phd-research-fellow-in-computational-neuroscience-brain-physics&#34;&gt;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/290338/phd-research-fellow-in-computational-neuroscience-brain-physics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The PhD project will focus on biophysical modeling of electrical and magnetic brain signals and the mechanisms through which externally applied fields influence neural dynamics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Master’s degree or equivalent in physics, computer science, mathematics or a mathematically-oriented engineering degreeForeign completed degree (M.Sc.-level) corresponding to a minimum of four years in the Norwegian educational systemExperience in mathematical modelling and programmingFluent oral and written communication skills in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Cover letterCVMaster’s degree transcriptNames of two referees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 9th December 2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; NOK from 550,800 - 595,000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-research-fellow-in-mobile-robotics-oslo&#34;&gt;PhD Research Fellow in Mobile Robotics (Oslo)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/290044/phd-research-fellow-in-mobile-robotics&#34;&gt;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/290044/phd-research-fellow-in-mobile-robotics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The PhD research fellow will work in the Autosender project, which aims to enhance multi-sensor situational awareness systems integrating them with an autonomous unmanned ground vehicle capable of navigating forest environments. The main goal is to develop and implement an intelligent autonomous solution for efficiently deploying and retrieving sensor nodes, with applications for both military and civilian purposes. The fellow will primarily work on robot development and autonomous navigation, along with opportunities to investigate planning and optimization of sensor placement, human-robot interaction, and operation in winter and arctic conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; requireddesiredlanguage_requirementgrade_requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV, cover letter, master’s degree diploma, and any relevant certificates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 1st of July 2025 for candidates without a master’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; The fellowship remuneration is consistent with the University of Oslo&amp;rsquo;s guidelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-research-fellowships-in-economics-oslo&#34;&gt;PhD Research Fellowships in Economics (Oslo)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/288169/phd-research-fellowships-in-economics&#34;&gt;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/288169/phd-research-fellowships-in-economics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; PhD Research Fellows will automatically be admitted to the Faculty of Social Sciences&amp;rsquo; PhD programme and benefit from the Faculty’s organized research training. The appointments are for a period of 4 years with 25% teaching and administrative duties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; The PhD candidate must hold a 2-year Master&amp;rsquo;s degree or an equivalent qualification in economics. Candidates completing their Master&amp;rsquo;s degrees in the spring semester of 2026 before August 1, 2026, may apply. GRE test is required for candidates from outside the EEA/EU, the UK, or Switzerland. Proof of proficiency in English is required, with TOEFL or IELTS tests except for certain exemptions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; The application must include a project proposal, proof of academic qualifications, GRE test results (if applicable), and documentation of English proficiency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 15th January 2026&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; NOK 555,000 to 601,000 per annum depending on qualifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS/AI PhD Jobs Update 2025-11-24</title>
      <link>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/phd_2025-11-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/phd_2025-11-24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-students-in-integrated-tn-ntn-6g-and-beyond-networks-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral students in integrated TN-NTN 6G and beyond networks (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/861362?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/861362?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Explore novel concepts for antenna cooperation and beamforming in satellite constellations to achieve high performance with low energy consumption.Address terrestrial–non-terrestrial (TN–NTN) integration and network design, with emphasis on architectures and protocols that enable seamless connectivity across ground, aerial, and satellite domains.Investigate the joint management of cloud, processing, and radio resources in space, targeting flexible orchestration of computing and communication to meet stringent performance and sustainability demands of future AI-driven applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (for example a master&amp;rsquo;s degree), or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, of which at least 60 second-cycle higher education credits.Acquired, in some other way within or outside the country, substantially equivalent knowledge.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.Goal-oriented and persevering in work.Ability to independently pursue work, collaborate with others, have a professional approach, analyze and work with complex issues, and communicate effectively in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterTranscriptsReferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-students-in-theoretical-foundations-of-data-storage-and-analysis-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral students in theoretical foundations of data storage and analysis (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869297?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869297?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The research team develops algorithms and data structures with provable guarantees, focusing on randomized algorithms and probabilistic data structures such as data sketches, Bloom filters, and hash functions. Students will spend a significant part of their work analyzing algorithms theoretically. Several directions of the project are possible and will be determined in collaboration with the Ph.D. candidate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Applicants must have basic eligibility for postgraduate education and hold or be about to receive a Master of Science degree. A suitable background includes degrees in computer science, mathematics, electrical engineering, or technical physics with a theoretical specialization. A strong background and passionate interest in algorithm design and mathematics, along with English proficiency, are mandatory. Previous participation in International Mathematical Olympiads or International Olympiads in Informatics is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledgeapplication letter (maximum 2 pages) describing research interests and academic backgroundcopies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-sic-bipolar-devices-for-power-electronics-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in SiC bipolar devices for power electronics (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868812?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868812?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Contribute to cutting-edge research on Silicon Carbide (SiC) Bipolar Junction Transistor (BJT) and Insulated Gate Bipolar Transistor (IGBT) devices for next-generation power electronics applications. Involve fabrication and characterization of new devices in KTH’s Electrum Laboratory with a focus on semiconductor process technology to enhance device performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Must have passed a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, including at least 60 second-cycle higher education credits, or acquired substantially equivalent knowledge. Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6. Experience of power semiconductor devices and semiconductor process technology is meritorious.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge, application letter (maximum 2 pages) describing academic interests, copies of diplomas and grades from previous studies, certificates of fulfilled language requirements, translations into English or Swedish (if necessary), certified copies of originals, and representative publications or technical reports with summaries and links to full texts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-machine-learning-for-robotic-manipulation-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Machine Learning for Robotic Manipulation (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869586?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869586?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Develop novel approaches for large scale real-world robotic manipulation experiments and benchmarkingestablish internationally relevant datasets and benchmarks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Must have a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s) or 240 higher education credits (including 60 second-cycle credits); mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6goal-oriented, able to collaborate and analyze complex issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVapplication letter (maximum 2 pages); representative publications or technical reports (with summary and web link for longer documents).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-electrochemical-sensing-and-control-for-organs-on-chips-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Electrochemical Sensing and Control for Organs-on-Chips (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/867956?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/867956?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The doctoral research project will focus on the design and development of electrochemical sensors and electrochemical actuators, along with the requisite testing and characterization. You will collaborate closely with other members of the multidisciplinary team on Organ-on-Chip integration and biological application. The project offers excellent potential for impactful publications and generating new IP, while providing opportunities to develop relevant interdisciplinary skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be admitted, the applicant must have passed a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits (including at least 60 second-cycle credits), or acquired substantially equivalent knowledge. Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6. Meritorious but not required: prior education or experience in electrochemistry and/or catalytic surface engineering.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies and certificates of fulfilled language requirements. Translations into English or Swedish if the original document is not issued in one of these languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-polymer-technology-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Polymer Technology (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868704?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868704?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The doctoral student will synthesize, integrate, and apply high-performance barrier layers to be used on moulded cellulose fibre products, as well as understand and model structure and properties during synthesis, lamination, use, and recycling. They will gain experience in fundamental research and practical application development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Mobility rules - Candidates must not have resided or conducted their main activity (work, studies, etc.) in Sweden for more than 12 months in the 3 years immediately preceding the recruitment date.Must have passed a second cycle degree (for example a master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, of which at least 60 second-cycle higher education credits, or acquired substantially equivalent knowledge.Completed university-level course in polymer chemistry, materials chemistry, or polymer technology.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterTranscriptsReferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement, including mobility allowance and possible family allowance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-solid-mechanics-modelling-of-cellulose-fibre-networks-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Solid Mechanics: Modelling of cellulose fibre networks (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869544?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869544?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Developing a physics-based numerical model for deformation and damage analysis in cellulose fiber networks, enabling advanced materials design and manufacturing tools. Addressing fundamental fiber network mechanics challenges and providing validated models for industry. Contributing to industrially relevant research and developing advanced computational and experimental skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Basic eligibility according to Swedish Higher Education Ordinance. Mobility rules: Candidates must not have resided or conducted their main activity in Sweden for more than 12 months in the 3 years preceding the recruitment date. Must hold a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or equivalent knowledge. Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6. Additional qualifications: Proficiency in numerical methods (FEM) and programming (Python, Matlab, C++, Fortran), background in mechanics of materials or computational modelling, interest in interdisciplinary collaboration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV, cover letter, copies of previous degrees, proof of English proficiency, and any other supporting documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement, with additional mobility and possible family allowances.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-solid-mechanics-with-a-focus-on-data-driven-methods-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Solid Mechanics with a focus on data-driven methods (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869595?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869595?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Create an AI-based hybrid tool for diagnosis and prognosis in the dry forming of cellulose fibresCombine experimental data with physics-based modelsBridge the gap between advanced simulations and industrial product developmentContribute to highly industrially relevant researchDevelop advanced computational and experimental skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Basic eligibility as per Swedish Higher Education Ordinance: second cycle degree or equivalent knowledgeMandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6Mobility rules: Candidates must not have resided or conducted their main activity in Sweden for more than 12 months in the 3 years immediately preceding the recruitment dateGoal oriented and persevering in workAbility to independently pursue work and collaborate with othersProfessional approach and ability to analyse and work with complex issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterTranscripts of recordsDiplomasOther relevant documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement, includes mobility allowance and possible family allowance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;double-degree-phd-student-in-chemistry-with-specialization-in-polymer-electrolytes-for-batteries-kth&#34;&gt;Double degree PhD student in Chemistry with specialization in polymer electrolytes for batteries (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869881?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869881?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Experimental studies of polymer electrolytes, primarily solid-state, for applications in Li-based batteriespolymer synthesis, electrolyte fabrication, construction and testing of prototype battery cellsmaterials characterization techniques and electrochemical characterization of electrolytes and cellscourse work and possible teaching or other departmental duties (maximum 20%).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (e.g., a master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits (including at least 60 second-cycle higher education credits); passed courses in chemistry or related disciplines totaling a minimum of 90 higher education credits (60 on an advanced level and at least 30 within chemistry); a degree project of at least 15 creditsEnglish equivalent to English B/6experiences with polymers and polymer materials, batteries (especially Li-batteries), and general experiences in materials chemistry and electrochemistry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Application to include educational qualifications, CV, letter of motivation, and references.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; The total length of employment may not exceed what corresponds to full-time doctoral education, typically four years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-advanced-characterisationmodelling-of-tungsten-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Advanced characterisation/modelling of tungsten (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/859676?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/859676?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Develop thermodynamic and kinetic descriptions of tungsten and its alloys.Integrate results into microstructure models to predict phase transformations and grain structure during electron beam powder bed fusion.Collaborate with experimental researchers to validate models and contribute to the development of crack-free tungsten components.Characterise tungsten and its alloys at the atomic level using techniques such as atom probe tomography (APT) and electron-ion microscopy.Identify and understand the effects of trace and alloying elements on microstructure and properties.Feed experimental data into models and contribute to the development of crack-free tungsten components.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Master’s degree in Materials Science or a related field.Basic eligibility in accordance with the Swedish Higher Education Ordinance.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.Mobility rules: Candidates must not have resided or conducted their main activity in Sweden for more than 12 months in the 3 years immediately preceding the recruitment date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterReference lettersMaster’s degree certificate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement, plus mobility allowance and possible family allowance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-students-in-theoretical-condensed-matter-physics-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral students in Theoretical Condensed Matter Physics (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/852011?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/852011?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Collaboration with local and international theoretical and experimental groups involved in the project. Supervision by Professor Egor Babaev. Ability to independently pursue work and collaborate with others, have a professional approach, and analyze and work with complex issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Basic eligibility requires either passed a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed at least 240 higher education credits (60 of which must be second-cycle). Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6. Personal skills assessment is emphasized during selection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge. Application letter (maximum 2 pages) describing why you want to pursue research, your academic interests, and how they relate to your previous studies and future goals. Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies and certificates of fulfilled language requirements. Translations into English or Swedish if applicable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-socio-technical-studies-of-conversational-robots-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Socio-technical studies of conversational robots (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/871088?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/871088?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct user studies on the integration of AI-driven conversational robots within elderly careExplore the benefits and tensions across technical, ethical, and regulatory aspectsAssess the impact of robots on care workflowsDevelop a proposal for a Nordic Model for sustainable robot integration in long-term carePublish results in high-quality peer-reviewed journalsPresent at scientific conferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (for example a master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, including at least 60 second-cycle higher education creditsMandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6Experience in conducting user studies with robots or AI-driven technologiesExperience in social science methodologiesGood communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studiesCertificates of fulfilled language requirementsCV including relevant professional experience and knowledgeApplication letter (maximum 2 pages long)Representative publications or technical reports with summaries for longer documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-astrophysics-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Astrophysics (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/866832?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/866832?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The PhD student will work in the field of supernova remnants, addressing questions related to explosion physics, compact objects, and circumstellar interaction. The work will primarily involve analysis and modelling of observational data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be admitted to postgraduate education, the applicant must have basic eligibility in accordance with either of the following: passed a second cycle degree (for example a master&amp;rsquo;s degree), or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, of which at least 60 are second-cycle higher education credits, or acquired, in some other way, substantially equivalent knowledge. The basic eligibility should be in either astronomy or physics. In addition, there is a mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6. Candidates are assessed on their ability to independently pursue their work, collaborate with others, and analyze and work with complex issues. Important experiences and skills include a MSc project in astronomy, experience in analysis of astronomical data, and excellent written and oral communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge.Application letter with a brief description of research interests (maximum 2 pages long).Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies and certificates of fulfilled language requirements (translations into English or Swedish if necessary).Representative publications or technical reports (with a summary and web link for longer documents).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received by the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-the-design-of-interaction-synchrony-with-soft-robotics-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in the Design of Interaction Synchrony with Soft Robotics (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868290?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868290?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Design and demonstrate robust prototypes for interaction synchrony with soft robotics.Work on the ERC-funded project &amp;lsquo;Intimate Touch&amp;rsquo; and the Digital Futures funded project &amp;lsquo;Redefining Mobility for Ageing Adults&amp;rsquo;.Design for touch and movement with new materials from the perspective of soma design.Develop and study applications in the real world related to soft robotics and haptic technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Human Computer Interaction or a related subject), or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, of which at least 60 are second-cycle higher education credits.Equivalent knowledge acquired in some other way within or outside the country.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.Ability to independently pursue work, collaborate with others, analyze complex issues, draw from critical feminist theories, utilize creative methods, and work in an interdisciplinary team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge.Application letter with a brief description of research interests (maximum 2 pages long).Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies and certificates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-architectural-technology-and-design-technologies-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Architectural Technology and Design Technologies (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868833?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/868833?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct advanced design technologies and design-based research.Participate in multiple research projects.Provide an individual research topic.Engage in teaching within the 1st and 2nd cycle of the architectural program.Collaborate in design processes and scholarly writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Basic eligibility according to Swedish Higher Education Ordinance.Passed a second cycle degree or 240 higher education credits.Minimum 60 second-cycle higher education credits.Mandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6.Experience as a practicing architect or computational design developer is a merit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledge.Application letter (maximum 2 pages long) describing motivation for research.Copies of diplomas and grades from previous university studies.Certificates of fulfilled language requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received at the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-probabilistic-machine-learning-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Probabilistic Machine Learning (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869866?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869866?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Work with open-source large-scale machine learning modelsDevelop theoretical and methodological work to improve the reliability and trustworthiness of machine learning modelsDevelop open-source librariesPublish in top-tier machine learning venuesCollaborate with researchers working on trustworthy machine learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, including at least 60 second-cycle higher education creditsStrong mathematical and programming skillsStrong background in machine learning, statistics, linear algebra, and optimizationFirst research experience through peer-reviewed publicationsMandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Copies of diplomasTranscripts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Midnight, CET/CEST (Central European Time/Central European Summer Time) on the last closing date&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-large-language-model-inferencing-kth&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Large Language Model inferencing (KTH)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869680?l=en&#34;&gt;https://www.kth.se/lediga-jobb/869680?l=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Design, implementation, and evaluation of distributed systems and networks for machine learning inferenceapplying machine learning concepts with the goal of devising agentic frameworks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Passed a second cycle degree (e.g., master&amp;rsquo;s degree) or completed course requirements of at least 240 higher education credits, with at least 60 second-cycle higher education creditsmandatory requirement for English equivalent to English B/6knowledge of systems and networking is highly desirable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV including relevant professional experience and knowledgeapplication letter (maximum 2 pages) explaining motivation for research studiescopies of diplomas and gradescertificates of fulfilled language requirementstranslations into English or Swedish if documents are not in these languagescertified copies of originalsrepresentative publications or technical reports with summaries and web links for longer documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications must be received by the last closing date at midnight, CET/CEST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary according to KTH’s Doctoral student salary agreement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-electrical-engineering-to-the-department-of-electrical-and-information-technology-pa20252605-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Electrical Engineering to the Department of Electrical and Information Technology  (PA2025/2605) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:856834/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:856834/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Perform research and teaching within the Cybersecurity and Privacy areaContribute to research projectsTake doctoral coursesParticipate in seminars and conferencesEngage in departmental work (maximum of 20% of working hours)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Awarded a second-cycle qualificationSatisfaction of requirements for courses comprising at least 240 credits (60 credits in the second cycle)Substantially equivalent knowledge in other areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterDegree certificatesTranscripts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-electrical-engineering-focusing-on-design-of-radio-frequency-integrated-circuits-to-the-department-of-electrical-and-information-technology-pa20253080-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Electrical Engineering focusing on design of radio frequency integrated circuits to the Department of Electrical and Information Technology (PA2025/3080) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:870960/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:870960/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; You will primarily devote yourself to your doctoral programme, which includes participation in research projects as well as third cycle courses, seminars and conferences. Your research will focus on design of radio frequency integrated circuits. You will then develop new solutions on circuit and architecture level, design and simulate circuits, design chip layout and passive components with EM-simulations, and set up and perform measurements in the lab. You will cooperate with other ELLIIT researchers, especially with the corresponding doctoral student in Linköping in analog and radio frequency integrated circuit design, and also with researchers in digital circuits and wireless systems. You will write scientific papers and present them at international conferences and publish in international journals. Furthermore, you will take doctoral student courses to deepen your knowledge in integrated circuit design, CAD-tools, wireless systems, and other relevant areas. The duties also include participation in teaching and other departmental work (however, a maximum of 20% of working hours).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be eligible for admission and employment as a doctoral student, you must fulfil the admission requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; You must submit relevant documents as part of your application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Application deadline is not specified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Salary details are not specified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-physics-within-thz-electron-spin-resonance-ellipsometry-pa20253292-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Physics within THz-electron spin resonance-ellipsometry (PA2025/3292) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:875564/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:875564/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; You will primarily devote yourself to your doctoral programme, which includes participation in research projects as well as third cycle courses, seminars and conferences. The aim of the PhD project is to conduct research in THz material analysis to expand the scope of THz ellipsometry and optical Hall effect to electron spin resonance ellipsometry. The method will mainly be applied in materials science, in particular for the investigation of crystal phases and defects in semiconductors. In addition to nitride material systems, a focus area will be Ga2O3 and other ultrawide bandgap semiconductors. The duties also include participation in teaching and other departmental work (however, a maximum of 20% of working hours).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; generalspecific&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-ethnology-pa20253093-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Ethnology (PA2025/3093) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871299/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871299/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studiesDepartmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Ethnology are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-archaeology-pa20253088-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Archaeology (PA2025/3088) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871269/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871269/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studiesDepartmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned (maximum 20% of the position).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Archaeology are specified in the general syllabus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan (all documents must be uploaded in PDF format).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-jewish-studies-with-a-specialisation-in-late-antiquity-pa20253089-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Jewish Studies with a Specialisation in Late Antiquity (PA2025/3089) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871280/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871280/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The successful candidate is expected to take an active part in the department’s seminars and research activities related to Late Antiquity. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned, with a maximum amount of such work set at 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Applicants should have their primary expertise in Judaism of Late Antiquity. Preference will be given to candidates who have also worked with Late Antique Christian sources or, in other ways, with Jewish–Christian interactions during the period approximately 200–700 CE. Projects that seek to integrate both textual and archaeological evidence are particularly welcome.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualifications, cover letter, records of previous studies, documentation of language skills, academic papers / degree projects, any scholarly publications, project plan. Please note that you need to upload all documents with your application in PDF format.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-practical-philosophy-pa20253090-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Practical Philosophy (PA2025/3090) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871286/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871286/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Practical Philosophy are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-cognitive-science-pa20253091-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Cognitive Science (PA2025/3091) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871290/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871290/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct doctoral studiesPerform departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks (maximum 20% of total work)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Cognitive Science as specified in the general syllabusApplicants&amp;rsquo; ability to benefit from doctoral studies assessed against criteria of quality, quantity, progression, and relevance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationsCover letterRecords of previous studiesDocumentation of language skillsAcademic papers / degree projectsAny scholarly publicationsProject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-human-rights-studies-pa20253092-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Human Rights Studies (PA2025/3092) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871292/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871292/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Human Rights Studies are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-old-testament-studies-or-in-philosophy-of-religion-and-ethics-pa20253108-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Old Testament Studies or in Philosophy of Religion and Ethics (PA2025/3108) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871350/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871350/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Actively participate in the relevant subject&amp;rsquo;s research seminarBe regularly present at the departmentConduct doctoral studiesDepartmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks (maximum 20%)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Old Testament Studies and in Philosophy of Religion and Ethics as specified in the respective general syllabusAbility to benefit from doctoral studies assessed against quality, quantity, progression, and relevance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationsCover letterRecords of previous studiesDocumentation of language skillsAcademic papers / degree projectsAny scholarly publicationsProject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-art-history-and-visual-studies-pa20253094-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Art History and Visual Studies (PA2025/3094) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871306/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871306/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Art History and Visual Studies are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-history-of-ideas-and-sciences-pa20253096-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in History of Ideas and Sciences (PA2025/3096) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871312/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871312/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in History of Ideas and Sciences are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against criteria of quality, quantity, progression and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-practical-theology-specialising-in-recruiting-for-professional-ministry-pa20253106-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Practical Theology, specialising in recruiting for professional ministry (PA2025/3106) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871347/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871347/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The doctoral student is expected to actively participate in the research seminar in Church History and Practical Theology at CTR, be regularly present at the department, and may also be required to carry out tasks for the Diocese of Växjö as part of their departmental duties, with a maximum of 20% assigned departmental work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Fluency in Swedish or another Scandinavian language is required. Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Practical Theology are specified in the general syllabus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-one-of-the-following-specialisations-french-studies-with-a-specialisation-in-didactics-french-studies-with-a-specialisation-in-linguistics-or-modern-greek-studies-with-a-specialisation-in-linguistics-pa20253097-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in one of the following specialisations: French Studies with a specialisation in Didactics, French Studies with a specialisation in Linguistics, or Modern Greek Studies with a specialisation in Linguistics (PA2025/3097) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871315/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871315/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Undertake doctoral studiesEngage in departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks (maximum 20% workload)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in French Studies and in Modern Greek Studies as specified in the respective general syllabusAssessment based on quality, quantity, progression, and relevance of the applicant&amp;rsquo;s ability to benefit from doctoral studies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationsCover letterRecords of previous studiesDocumentation of language skillsAcademic paper / degree projectsAny scholarly publicationsProject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-literature-pa20253098-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Literature (PA2025/3098) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871320/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871320/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies. Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Good proficiency in Swedish is required. Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Literature are specified in the general syllabus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-media-history-within-the-national-graduate-school-of-historical-studies-pa20253105-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Media History, within The National Graduate School of Historical Studies (PA2025/3105) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871344/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871344/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies.Departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in Media History are specified in the general syllabus.The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against the criteria of quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-general-linguistics-pa20253099-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in General Linguistics (PA2025/3099) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871325/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871325/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studies and departmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in General Linguistics are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-english-literature-pa20253101-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in English Literature (PA2025/3101) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871330/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871330/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studiesDepartmental work such as teaching and administrative tasks (up to 20%)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Ability to benefit from doctoral studies assessed against quality, quantity, progression and relevanceSpecific entry requirements as per the general syllabus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationsCover letterRecords of previous studiesDocumentation of language skillsAcademic papers / degree projectsAny scholarly publicationsProject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-slavic-languages-with-a-specialisation-in-polish-literature-or-ukrainian-literature-pa20253102-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in Slavic Languages with a specialisation in Polish Literature or Ukrainian Literature (PA2025/3102) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871331/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871331/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studiesDepartmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks (maximum of 20%)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements specified in the general syllabusKnowledge of contemporary Ukrainian literature or Polish literatureComparative research projects involving both Polish and Ukrainian literatures will be given priority&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationsCover letterRecords of previous studiesDocumentation of language skillsAcademic papers / degree projectsAny scholarly publicationsProject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-history-within-the-national-graduate-school-of-historical-studies-pa20253103-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in History, within The National Graduate School of Historical Studies (PA2025/3103) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871337/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:871337/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Doctoral studiesDepartmental work, such as teaching and administrative tasks, can be assigned. The maximum amount of such work is 20%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Entry requirements for doctoral studies in History are specified in the general syllabus. The selection process will primarily take into account the applicants’ ability to benefit from doctoral studies, assessed against the criteria quality, quantity, progression, and relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CV / list of qualificationscover letterrecords of previous studiesdocumentation of language skillsacademic papers / degree projectsany scholarly publicationsproject plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 20.Dec.2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Monthly salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-student-in-working-environment-with-a-focus-on-digitalisation-pa20252877-lund&#34;&gt;PhD student in working environment, with a focus on digitalisation (PA2025/2877) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:865044/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:865044/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Devote yourself primarily to the doctoral programmeParticipate in research projects and third cycle courses, seminars, and conferencesConduct literature reviews on mental ill-health among children and young peopleCarry out semi-structured interviews and focus-group discussions with psychologists and school counsellorsAnalyze how digitalization affects workload and professional responsibilityProduce guidance material that documents project and research resultsTest results with target groups through feedback meetingsContribute to teaching and other departmental work (up to 20% of working time)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Fulfill general admission requirements for third-cycle courses and study programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVMotivation letterTranscriptsReferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-student-in-theoretical-computer-science-andor-combinatorial-optimization-pa20253338-lund&#34;&gt;Doctoral student in theoretical computer science and/or combinatorial optimization (PA2025/3338) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:876903/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:876903/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; You will primarily devote yourself to your doctoral programme, which includes participation in research projects as well as third cycle courses, seminars and conferences. The main tasks and responsibilities consist of conducting mathematical research and/or algorithm design and development. The work duties also include teaching and other departmental duties (no more than 20%), in which case the position is prolonged accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be eligible for admission and employment as a doctoral student, you must fulfil the requirements below. A person meets the general admission requirements for third-cycle courses and study programmes if the applicant has been awarded a second-cycle qualification, or has satisfied the requirements for courses comprising at least 240 credits of which at least 60 credits were awarded in the second cycle, or has acquired substantially equivalent knowledge in some other way in Sweden or abroad. Applicants meet the specific admission requirements for third cycle studies in computer science if they have at least 60 second-cycle credits at an advanced level with relevance for the research topic, or an MSc in Engineering in Computer Science and Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Information and Communication Technology, Engineering Physics or Engineering.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-in-sociology-of-law--authoritarian-governance-in-central-asia-pa20253055-lund&#34;&gt;PhD in Sociology of Law – Authoritarian Governance in Central Asia (PA2025/3055) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:870095/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:870095/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct independent research within the scope of the project.Undertake fieldwork in Central Asia and two mandatory secondments (one academic, one non-academic) abroad.Participate in training events, workshops, and conferences organized by the SOCIAL Doctoral Network.Collaborate with international supervisors and peers.Contribute to departmental activities, including teaching and seminars (up to 20% of working hours).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; A completed degree at the advanced level in Sociology of Law or another subject deemed relevant by the employer.Doctoral candidates cannot have been awarded a doctoral degree and/or completed more than four years of full-time equivalent research experience.A minimum of 240 credits, of which at least 60 must be at the advanced level.At least 30 credits in Sociology of Law or a related subject at the advanced level, including a thesis of at least 15 credits.Excellent ability to express yourself in spoken and written English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterTranscriptsOther relevant documents as specified in the application guidelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-in-sociology-of-authoritarian-law--outside-the-law-legal-mobilization-in-central-asia-pa20253042-lund&#34;&gt;PhD in Sociology of Authoritarian Law – “Outside the Law” Legal Mobilization in Central Asia (PA2025/3042) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:869875/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:869875/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct independent research within the scope of the project.Undertake fieldwork in Central Asia and two mandatory secondments (one academic, one non-academic) abroad.Participate in training events, workshops, and conferences organized by the SOCIAL Doctoral Network.Collaborate with international supervisors and peers.Contribute to departmental activities, including teaching and seminars (up to 20% of working hours).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; A completed degree at the advanced level in Sociology of Law or another subject deemed relevant by the employer.Doctoral candidates cannot have been awarded a doctoral degree and/or completed more than four years of full-time equivalent research experience.Must meet general entry requirements for third cycle courses and study programmes, including having been awarded a second cycle qualification or equivalent knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; CVCover letterCopy of degree certificateReference letters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;at-least-one-phd-position-at-the-sociology-of-law-department-pa20253009-lund&#34;&gt;At least one PHD position at the Sociology of Law Department (PA2025/3009) (Lund)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:868967/type:job/where:4/apply:1&#34;&gt;https://lu.varbi.com/en/what:job/jobID:868967/type:job/where:4/apply:1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Focus on PhD studies and work on dissertation in Sociology of Law.Participate in the department’s research environment.Perform teaching and administrative duties up to a maximum of 20% of full-time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Master’s degree in Sociology of Law or another relevant subject.Minimum of 240 ECTS credits, with at least 60 at the advanced level.At least 30 ECTS credits in Sociology of Law at an advanced level, including at least 15 credits in a thesis.Excellent ability to express yourself in spoken and written English.Strong motivation and ability to work independently under pressure.Good collaboration and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Cover letter in Swedish or English (max 1,000 words).Thesis equivalent to at least 15 ECTS credits at the advanced level.CV in Swedish or English showing eligibility for PhD studies.Degree certificates and transcripts in Swedish or English.A brief research plan of max 13,000 characters in Swedish or English.Names and contact details of two referees.Any other relevant documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified in the provided text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Fixed-term employment, four years according to the Higher Education Ordinance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-position-in-experimental-physics-umea&#34;&gt;PhD position in  Experimental Physics (Umea)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/phd-position-in-experimental-physics_869672/&#34;&gt;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/phd-position-in-experimental-physics_869672/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The candidate will be engaged in synthesis of new materials and characterization of these materials using BET/DFT surface area analysis, DSC, x-ray diffraction, Raman and IR spectroscopy etc. It is also planned to use synchrotron radiation facilities. Teaching and other departmental work (up to a maximum of 20%) can be included.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be admitted for studies at third-cycle level you are required to have completed a second-cycle level degree or completed course requirements of at least 240 ECTS credits, of which 60 are at second-cycle level (Master’s level), or equivalent education from abroad. In addition to these requirements, 120 ECTS need to be within the physics subject area. Applicants with master degrees in other subjects, such as Chemistry, Material Science or Physical Engineering, are also welcomed to apply if the above requirements are fulfilled. Competence and experience in experimental research, including material synthesis, material characterization, and spectroscopy, are considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; A cover letter with summary of research interests and motivation (max. 1 page)Curriculum VitaeCertified copies of relevant degree certificate(s) translated to English or SwedishTranscripts with grades, with English or Swedish translation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2025-12-01&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Fixed according to the established salary level for doctoral students&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-position-in-chemistry-with-a-specialization-in-environmental-chemistry-umea&#34;&gt;PhD position in Chemistry, with a specialization in Environmental Chemistry (Umea)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/phd-position-in-chemistry-with-a-specialization-in-environmental-chemistry_871188/&#34;&gt;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/phd-position-in-chemistry-with-a-specialization-in-environmental-chemistry_871188/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The thesis project will focus on the fate of PFAS in thermochemical conversion and associated processes of biomass and industrial waste materials. The research will be conducted in close collaboration with our industry partner Netherlands Organization for Applied Scientific Research (TNO), and will include combustion experiments in lab set-ups, using real and model waste feedstocks. Some of the experimental studies will be conducted in lab-scale setups at the Department of Chemistry but given TNO’s unique infrastructure we will also have the possibility to complement the lab studies with realistic and upscaled experiments and sampling campaigns at their development facilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; To be admitted for studies at third-cycle level you are required to have completed a second-cycle level degree, or completed course requirements of at least 240 ECTS credits, of which at least 60 ECTS credits are at second-cycle level or have an equivalent education from abroad, or equivalent qualifications. To fulfill the specific entry requirements to be admitted for studies at third-cycle level in chemistry, you are required to have completed first-cycle courses of at least 90 ECTS credits within the field of chemistry or another subject considered to be directly relevant to the specialization in question. Very good command of the English language, both written and spoken. Training and/or experience in environmental chemistry, analytical chemistry, combustion chemistry, organic chemistry is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Please submit your application including a CV, a cover letter, and other relevant documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-02&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Temporary position, full-time (100%)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-2-phd-students-for-the-department-of-political-science-umea&#34;&gt;1-2 PhD students for the Department of Political Science (Umea)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/1-2-phd-students-for-the-department-of-political-science_860718/&#34;&gt;https://www.umu.se/en/work-with-us/open-positions/1-2-phd-students-for-the-department-of-political-science_860718/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct research on a topic relevant to political science or peace and conflict studies, develop a research plan, and participate in departmental activities. The position allows for teaching or other departmental activities up to 20% of the time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Applicants must have a degree at the advanced level with at least 240 ECTS points, including 60 ECTS points at the advanced level and 90 ECTS points in peace and conflict studies or political science. Proficiency in both oral and written communication in English is required. The evaluation includes previous academic performance, quality of writing samples and project plan, analytical skills, communicative skills, critical skills, independence, and ability to complete tasks within a given time frame.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; A cover letter summarizing qualifications, research interests, and reasons for applying (max two pages)A research proposal of 3-5 pages discussing potential research problem, purpose, theory, and empirical dataCV / curriculum vitaeCertified transcripts of academic records and degrees1-3 writing samples in Swedish or English, such as B.A. thesis, master’s thesis, or academic publications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 2026-01-30&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Temporary position, full-time, equivalent to four years of full-time studies (240 ECTS).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;doctoral-researcher--masters-thesis-worker-ringo--piston-ring-dynamics-measurement-for-understanding-and-reducing-lube-oil-transport-aalto&#34;&gt;Doctoral Researcher / Master’s Thesis Worker RingO – Piston Ring Dynamics Measurement for Understanding and Reducing Lube Oil Transport (Aalto)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aalto.fi/en/open-positions/doctoral-researcher-masters-thesis-worker-ringo-piston-ring-dynamics-measurement-for-understanding&#34;&gt;https://www.aalto.fi/en/open-positions/doctoral-researcher-masters-thesis-worker-ringo-piston-ring-dynamics-measurement-for-understanding&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Conduct research on piston ring dynamics measurement for understanding and reducing lube oil transport.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in engineering or a related fieldstrong analytical and problem-solving skillsexperience with experimental work and data analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Curriculum VitaeCover letterAcademic transcriptsRecommendation letters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications will be accepted until the position is filled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Salary will be determined based on the applicant&amp;rsquo;s experience and qualifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-research-fellow-in-pharmaceutical-analytical-chemistry-oslo&#34;&gt;PhD Research Fellow in (Pharmaceutical) analytical chemistry (Oslo)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/289658/phd-research-fellow-in-pharmaceutical-analytical-chemistry&#34;&gt;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/289658/phd-research-fellow-in-pharmaceutical-analytical-chemistry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The candidate will work with implementing Molecularly Imprinted Polymers (MIPs) in the sample preparation workflow of bottom-up liquid chromatography-mass spectrometry (LC-MS) analysis of established disease biomarkers. Novel MIP-assays developed in the project will be validated against conventional assays including both immunoassays where available and MS-based assays. The project will mainly be conducted at the Department of Pharmacy, University of Oslo (UiO), but will include secondments (total approximately 6 months) to Proteome Sciences, Frankfurt (Germany), University of Strathclyde, Glasgow (United Kingdom) and Capitainer AB (Sweden).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Master’s degree or equivalent in (bio)analytical chemistry at the moment of appointment.Foreign completed degree (M.Sc.-level) corresponding to a minimum of four years in the Norwegian educational system in (bio)analytical chemistry.Experience with LC-MS and sample preparation (SPE or immuno-based affinity extractions) preferable from biological samples.Candidates must not have a doctoral degree at the date of recruitment.Fluent oral and written communication skills in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Cover letterCVCertificatesMaster’s thesisList of publications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 30th November 2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Not specified&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-research-fellow-in-computational-neurosciencebrain-physics-oslo&#34;&gt;PhD Research Fellow in computational neuroscience/brain physics (Oslo)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/290338/phd-research-fellow-in-computational-neuroscience-brain-physics&#34;&gt;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/290338/phd-research-fellow-in-computational-neuroscience-brain-physics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The PhD project will focus on biophysical modeling of electrical and magnetic brain signals and the mechanisms through which externally applied fields influence neural dynamics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Master’s degree or equivalent in physics, computer science, mathematics or a mathematically-oriented engineering degreeForeign completed degree (M.Sc.-level) corresponding to a minimum of four years in the Norwegian educational systemExperience in mathematical modelling and programmingFluent oral and written communication skills in EnglishPrevious experience in computational neuroscience (desired qualification)Good oral and written communication skills in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Application letterCVMaster&amp;rsquo;s thesisTranscripts of recordsList of publications (if applicable)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 9th December 2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; NOK from 550,800 - 595,000, depending on competence and experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-research-fellow-in-mobile-robotics-oslo&#34;&gt;PhD Research Fellow in Mobile Robotics (Oslo)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/290044/phd-research-fellow-in-mobile-robotics&#34;&gt;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/290044/phd-research-fellow-in-mobile-robotics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; The PhD research fellow will work on robot development and autonomous navigation as part of the Autosender project. Opportunities include investigating planning and optimization of sensor placement, human-robot interaction, operation in winter and arctic conditions, and use of communication nodes in addition to sensor packages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; requireddesiredgrade_requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Curriculum vitae (CV)Cover letterMaster&amp;rsquo;s degree certificateTranscriptsPublications (if any)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 1st of July 2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Fellowship period is three years. A fourth year may be considered and involves 25% other career-promoting work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-research-fellowship-in-political-science-3-4-years-oslo&#34;&gt;PhD Research Fellowship in Political Science (3-4 years) (Oslo)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/288543/phd-research-fellowship-in-political-science-3-4-years&#34;&gt;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/288543/phd-research-fellowship-in-political-science-3-4-years&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; Develop a research project within the thematic scope of the GETGOV project focusing on governing elites.Submit a project proposal including a thematic framework and at least three ideas for academic articles.Contribute to data collection and analyze the relationship between democratization and the composition of governing elites.Investigate the impact of governing elites on outcomes.Submit a career development plan within one month of the fellowship commencement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Education equivalent to five years at university level in Norway, including two years (120 credits) at Master&amp;rsquo;s level in a relevant field.MA thesis must be equivalent to at least half a year&amp;rsquo;s workload (30 ECTS).Relevant education in research methods.Strong English language skills (written and oral).Robust empirical research knowledge within political science.Proficient in conducting quantitative analyses.Experience with large language models, machine learning, and/or programming in R or equivalent is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Curriculum Vitae (CV)Project proposal including thematic and theoretical framework and ideas for academic articlesCareer development plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 24th November 2025&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; Salary according to the university&amp;rsquo;s salary scale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-research-fellowships-in-economics-oslo&#34;&gt;PhD Research Fellowships in Economics (Oslo)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/288169/phd-research-fellowships-in-economics&#34;&gt;https://www.jobbnorge.no/en/available-jobs/job/288169/phd-research-fellowships-in-economics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt; 3-5 PhD Research Fellow positions for the PhD programme are available at the Department of Economics. The appointments are for a period of 4 years with 25% teaching and administrative duties. PhD Research Fellows will be automatically admitted to the Faculty of Social Sciences&amp;rsquo; PhD programme and benefit from the Faculty’s organized research training.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt; Proven academic record: The PhD candidate must hold a 2-year Master&amp;rsquo;s degree (including master’s dissertation) or an equivalent qualification in economics. Accounting, auditing, business, marketing or management do not count as economics.Candidates completing their Master&amp;rsquo;s degrees (or equivalent) in the spring semester 2026 before August 1, 2026, may apply.Candidates must document qualifications based on detailed course descriptions and syllabuses if they have a degree from an institution other than the University of Oslo.Candidates who have completed a PhD program in Economics will not be accepted.Candidates who have already been accepted to a PhD program in Economics must inform about this.Candidates from institutions that do not use ECTS grades must include an official conversion of their grades to ECTS grades.For candidates with education from an institution outside the European Economic Area/the European Union, the UK or Switzerland, a recent score from the general GRE test is required.Proof of proficiency in English is required, which can be documented by taking either TOEFL or IELTS test.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documents:&lt;/strong&gt; Valid Master&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent qualificationsDetailed course descriptions and syllabuses (if applicable)GRE test result (if applicable)Proof of proficiency in English (TOEFL/IELTS or equivalent)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline:&lt;/strong&gt; 15th January 2026&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary/Contract:&lt;/strong&gt; NOK 555,000 to 601,000 per annum depending on qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DP_Question</title>
      <link>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/dp_question/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 18:20:59 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/dp_question/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;preface&#34;&gt;Preface&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because I always hit a wall with Dynamic Programming problems,  I would like to summarize the solution to Dynamic Programming problems(DP).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Basic solution to DP problems：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Initial State&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;State Transition Equation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;1--linear-dp&#34;&gt;1.  Linear DP&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. 1 Example：Leetcode 300.  Longest Increasing Subsequence&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Given an integer array nums,  return the length of the longest strictly increasing subsequence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example 1:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Input:&lt;/strong&gt; nums = [10, 9, 2, 5, 3, 7, 101, 18]&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Output:&lt;/strong&gt; 4&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Explanation:&lt;/strong&gt; The longest increasing subsequence is [2, 3, 7, 101],  therefore the length is 4.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Study Notes</title>
      <link>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/markdown_study_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 17:31:12 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://garyforreal.me/en/posts/study/markdown_study_notes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;preface&#34;&gt;Preface&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article mainly summarizes the common syntax of Markdown, so that you can write Markdown files better by yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;1-basic-grammer&#34;&gt;1. Basic Grammer&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;11-title&#34;&gt;1.1 Title&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use&lt;code&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; to create a title. The number of &lt;code&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; you use indicates the number of heading levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Markdown&lt;/th&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Display&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;# title1&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;title1&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;# title2&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;h2&gt;title2&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;# title3&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;title3&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;12-line-break&#34;&gt;1.2 Line break&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add &lt;code&gt;2 or more spaces&lt;/code&gt; after the text, or &lt;code&gt;add a blank line&lt;/code&gt; (press enter twice).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
